[
    {"question":"canape","ans":"ソファー" },
    {"question":"lit","ans":"ベット" },
    {"question":"le stylo (a bille)","ans":"ボールペン"},
    {"question":"cahier","ans":"ノト"},
    {"question":"calendrier","ans":"カレンダ"},
    {"question":"radio","ans":"ラジオ"},
    {"question":"chaine hifi","ans":"ステレオ"},
    {"question":"TV","ans":"テレビ"},
    {"question":"TV","ans":"テレビジョン"},
    {"question":"Appareil photo","ans":"カメラ"},
    {"question":"Ordinateur","ans":"コンピュタ"},
    {"question":"PC","ans":"パソコン"},
    {"question":"climatiseur","ans":"エアコン"},
    {"question":"Telecommande","ans":"リモコン"},
    {"question":"Carte Banquaire","ans":"クレジットカード"},
    {"question":"La porte","ans":"ドア"},
    {"question":"La lampe","ans":"ランプ"},
    {"question":"La table","ans":"タボル"},
    {"question":"La fourchette","ans":"フォーク"},
    {"question":"Le couteau","ans":"ナイフ"},
    {"question":"la cuillère","ans":"スプーン"},
    {"question":"toillettes","ans":"トイレ"}
    
]